[
  {
    "Question": "Who is the EZBot main Dev?",
    "Answer": "Chris1"
  },
  {
	"Question": "___ eats N00bs for lunch.",
	"Answer": "Xires"
  },
  {
	"Question": "Who is Evilzone's Symphorophiliac Programmer?",
	"Answer": "Kenjoe41"
  },
    {
	"Question": "Who is Evilzone's Symphorophiliac Programmer?",
	"Answer": "Kenjoe41"
  },
    {
	"Question": "In what year was the specification for the COBOL language created?",
	"Answer": "1959"
  },
    {
	"Question": "puddi is a",
	"Answer": "fag"
  },
    {
	"Question": "A popular scripting language for computers, often run in web browsers to create or alter dynamic content. It was developed by Brandan Eich for Netscape in 1995.",
	"Answer": "Javascript"
  },
    {
	"Question": "What does the C stand for in the equation E=mc2?",
	"Answer": "Speed of light"
  },
    {
	"Question": "What does the C stand for in the equation E=mc2?",
	"Answer": "Speed of light"
  },
    {
	"Question": "Actor: _____ bacon",
	"Answer": "Kevin"
  },
    {
	"Question": "Which element is also known as Quicksilver?",
	"Answer": "Mercury"
  }
]
